A Guide to the Huddle Family Papers, 1854-1970
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Box 10: Charles Huddle, Sr. Professional Papers, Business Records/Documents
  - Ivanhoe Invoices and Correspondence with Diamond Drilling Company (Box-folder 10-18)
  - H. C. Parce Correspondence (Box-folder 10-19)
  - Mineral Property Correspondence Virginia, Tennessee, and North Carolina Reports (Box-folder 10-20)
  - Reports From A. B. Dally Jr. (Box-folder 10-21)
  - Harrison Manganese Co. Reports (Box-folder 10-22)
  - Correspondence With H. C. Parse Concerning Mine Business (Box-folder 10-23)
  - Mining Reports (Box-folder 10-24)
  - Mining Reports and Property Correspondence (Box-folder 10-25)
  - Documents Concerning Midvale Mine Rockbridge County, Virginia (Box-folder 10-26)
  - Investigation Yancy County, Green Mountain, Bornsville, Spruce Pine, North Carolina (Box-folder 10-27)
  - Correspondence Regarding Mining Prospects in North Carolina (Box-folder 10-28)
  - Manganese Property Midvale Mine (Box-folder 10-29)
  - C. R. Huddle Personal Letters to Engineers (Box-folder 10-30)
  - Copies of Contracts (Box-folder 10-31)
  - C. R. Huddle Professional Engineer Correspondence- Air Reduction (Box-folder 10-32)
  - C. R. Huddle Correspondence With Engineers (Box-folder 10-33)
  - Miscellaneous Papers and Photographs (Box-folder 10-34)
  - C. R. Huddle Papers and Correspondence, 1920-1940 (Box-folder 10-30)
- Ivanhoe Mining and Smelting Corporation Ledger (Box-folder 11-1)
- Mining maps (oversize) (Folder 1)
- National Carbide 6, Ivanhoe Plant, Drawings Series 24-xxxx, 1929-1945 (Folder 2)
- Land and Factory Drawings, 1913-1929 (Folder 3)
- New River Mineral Company and National Carbide Company, Ivanhoe, Virginia, 1887-1955 (Folder 4)
- National Carbide Corporation, Ivanhoe, Virginia, A, D, & G series drawings, 1917-1918 (Folder 5)
- National Carbide Corporation Plant in Ivanhoe, Virginia, E & G series drawings, 1918 (Folder 6)